beckershospitalreview.com 2019-12-04

# Privacy Policy

\- Wednesday, May 30th, 2018[ Print ](https://www.beckershospitalreview.com/privacy-policy.html?tmpl=component&print=1&layout=default "Print article < Privacy Policy >") | [Email](https://www.beckershospitalreview.com/component/mailto/?tmpl=component&template=beckers&aid=128766&link=https://www.beckershospitalreview.com/privacy-policy.html)

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Becker's Hospital Review. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:

\- What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.  
\- What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.  
\- The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.  
\- How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

 **Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via our forms. We may share your information with our advertisers.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

 **Your Access to and Control Over Information**

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

\- See what data we have about you, if any.  
\- Change/correct any data we have about you.  
\- Have us delete any data we have about you.  
\- Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

 **Security**

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as your personal information), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the Web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 1.800.417.2035 or via email at [becker@beckershealthcare.com](mailto:becker@beckershealthcare.com).

_© Copyright ASC COMMUNICATIONS 2019. Interested in LINKING to or REPRINTING this content? View our policies by[clicking here](https://www.beckershospitalreview.com/linking-and-reprinting-policy.html)._

**To receive the latest hospital and health system business and legal news and analysis from _Becker's Hospital Review_ , sign-up for the free _Becker's Hospital Review E-weekly_ by [clicking here](https://www.beckershospitalreview.com/sign-up-for-our-free-e-weeklies.html).**
